Find a man, let's hear the financial
paper, the behavior of people as they interact with one another in markets.
Fires and sellers interact with each other in markets.
And the buyers and sellers that interact with each other are eventually going to determine
what actually is sold.
The price that he has sold and how much is it so.
Mark.
It's an easy part. [inaudible]
[inaudible]
[inaudible] I need to see that all the things. Can you say something like this?
[LAUGHTER]
[INAUDIBLE]
Hey.
I wish I had you.
[INAUDIBLE]
I really don't know.
I think all the time. (indistinct)
(indistinct) - Thanks far.
Bias.
As you might expect,
instead of walking aside,
but not producing any news,
biogenes and determined demands. And then sellers are going to argue As you might expect, it's the general sign that I'm producing anything new. Why is it in the determined demand?
And then sellers are going to
all will please then determine supply.
Now we're going to do it quickly.
We're going to have graph A and graph B. And this is going to be a demand graph.
And this is going to be a supply graph.
What we are going to focus on when we focus on supply and demand is this graph.
Together. together. However, what we're focusing on first is we're going to break any steps.
We're going to focus on demand first, then we're going to focus on supply,
and then we're going to work together, talk about how they interact together.
But first step, second step, third step.
We will need to know how this graph goes from here to a point there.
We're all going to need to know how this graph demand goes to there, and you guys get up to do this.
And this graph goes to there, there, there.
Okay.
Mind the light coming. But right now, we'll put the thing on this banana. That's not a big one to buy and they'll bring it together.
Okay, what is the market then?
A competitive market.
It makes the market in which there are many buyers and sellers.
Market is where there are many buyers and sellers.
So each has a negligible impact on the market price.
And then we can know what being supposed to be insignificant. Okay. That's the market definition definition so on and so forth.
Now let's get to what exactly is the main,
how do we use the finance, how do they move,
what exactly is this so on and so on and so on.
Let's see, come on. (clears throat) I'm sure she understood you're right nice for what movies
They model them after you.
You were above. [laughter]
[laughter]
It's not about fail.
It's not about a little bit of shit.
It's about the past failed. It's not about it. It will be a shit. There's no ask-tense thing about it.
What about the future?
I think that would be bad.
Thank you.
I'm wearing a little bit bigger.
Have you ever signed down on the third?
All I have to do is just flex a little bit.
- I'm interested in your regard. (indistinct)
- Let me live in Hylolomand.
Yeah, this is my problem.
- Okay, Doming, here's where it's gonna get
a little bit confusing to some of you.
This says quantity demanded.
Quantity demanded are two different day.
About us.
Okay.
How about that? - Okay, quantity demanded is the following.
It's simply the amount of the virus going to the world
of purchase, that's it, please simple.
It's really simple, quantity demanded is actually
I'm good, the virus willing to enable your purchase.
If you want to purchase 15 bottles of protein shakes
before you get to the gym,
- Yes.
- Go buy them.
- A lot of things.
- That is a sign.
- What I buy about a week, man.
- Thank you.
- The gym will burn before.
- They have to like kick other people out.
They don't get too soft.
Just very much.
They reserve.
You have to call that.
You should.
And then they like everyone.
They're like taking notes soon. 20 minutes.
Now the law of demand is following.
The law of demand states.
Now this is where a lot of students are going to be getting to get to the president for
the next couple minutes or a couple weeks rather.
So I'm going to get off this for a moment, okay?
It states that all are illegal and in economic terms there's a lack of order that we use in economics
of called setter as parents.
Setter as parents, and I'm gonna get off this screen for a moment,
so I'm gonna go back, because I'm gonna talk about setter as parents.
Setter as parents simply mean that all other things are equal,
then so it's gonna happen.
Now, what you guys are gonna do is you guys are gonna sit there
and you're gonna see economics term, I told you,
I'm gonna get off this screen for a moment. You guys are gonna see economics term you guys are going to sit there and you're going to see economics term. I told you I'm going to get off the screen for a moment. You guys are going to see economics
term and you're going to sit and you're going to analyze it too much. You're going to have paralysis.
You're going to say well this is a photo, well this is going to happen right and then this is
going to happen and what it is that's not going to matter to you. Not going to warn you right now.
You're going to have to be very careful in that mindset and economics. Economics assumes
that the first alternative is the answer,
not the second alternative, but the third alternative,
or the what is the alternative.
And the example I give all the time is I
ask you guys to come to front and the question is,
is what color is this guy?
What?
So if I gave everyone a test question,
so what color is the sky?
I think that all of you have red blue.
Here's the one, so what if it's black?
The blue.
What if it's night?
The silver blue?
What if it's very cloudy?
It's a silver blue, it's a little bright.
It's very, um, cloudy. It's a sublucous or a little bright.
Well, I'm excited about the progression.
Well, great, right?
You see how I can say the what if, what if, what if, what if, what if,
just because I say what if it doesn't disprove you with both,
that the sky is generally considered blue.
An economics income to that track.
You're going to say, oh,, well, there's been some increases. But the person gets laid off. The one of the first
accounts on board is what is this out? That's not the economic, from how economics
functions. Economics, as the word, is setters, parabas, being at all in it. People are not
talking about any of the what is the size of the law demand state is that
for all other things people and we're not playing a lot of games, we're not playing
all these other variables. The quantity demanded of a good is going to fall with the price of
that good prices. I will see what the market is, the price increases their um, coffee,
What market is voice increases their copy by one more dollar on the top going market choice and buying it for one more dollar
As the price increases, quantity demanded is going to be there
Pretty simple we can buy less things at the market bundle and senior talk with such starts charging me 15 dollars of a redo
What do you think I'm gonna do
for the quantity demanded in my personal life?
Increase and decrease.
Please, huh?
Increase, no, I'm gonna increase this
and you can't go as free and delicious.
Okay, good joke.
Okay, I would decrease my consumption
of senior thought about eating the next list of delicious
and I'll over my heart.
I just can't afford a $15 burrito.
I don't want someone else to worry.
But something you may not have
because you're gonna call the price of good prices.
Re-simple.
(mumbles)
See you over here.
Okay, all right.
On a graph, very, very simple.
This is a demand schedule.
All we're going to do is look at a graph on how the price of an ice cream cone and the
wants to keep demanded is going to be graphed.
So at $399, we expect 12.
As the price increases to 50 cents, well, our quantity of demand is going to be a little
bit less.
Notice I'm saying quantity of demand and I'm not saying demand.
If our price increases to a dollar,
or quantity demanded is going to be eight.
Prices increase, quantity demanded decreases.
Pretty simple.
You have to know that.
Okay.
And let's talk about the demand curve.
The demand curve is simply a demand, a demand schedule graph.
It's a graph of the relationship between a price of a good and a quantity of random.
So if I say let's drop some demand curves today.
We need to know that it is simply by someone access quantity demanded on another axis.
That's it.
What is this using? Is that a thing?
You know what the delay is?
You're not in it. (indistinct)
- It's a small fan, it's 9B. It's not the nice thing. I think I might be.
Stop the nice.
[INAUDIBLE]
You used to have a lot of-- well, this is-- I think you'll hold it recently.
Okay, that's the manager.
Everyone.
I think it says yes.
Okay.
Now, let's see what that demand schedule, how it looks graph.
You guys know if I gave you this, this demand schedule, you could graph that.
Yeah, for example, put price on one side, quantity on the other side, plot it.
Okay, for example, it's just going to look like this.
Price and I could come as it goes up our quantity. Our quantity management is going to go down. All we're going to do is put that--
those won't be wrapped.
Put them on the table like that.
I just put it as an assignment.
[INAUDIBLE]
[INAUDIBLE] OK, press the nice and jump. There it is, it's yours, it's not something.
Okay, press the nice button. There it is.
Now, notice, if we move from this point to this point,
any point along the line, the only way we move is based on the price.
And that is where you're going to get confused.
Price moves it. Price does not shift it. on price and that is where you're going to get confused. Right? Move.
So price does not shift it.
What moves along the line?
Price.
That is where you're going to get very, very confused.
So price affects quantity demanded.
Price is not going to affect demand.
And careful with the language price equals movement boxy demand
Okay, let's talk about market managers individual man. This is very simple market demand
But first it's not the whole individual demands for particular good or service all the sum people the economics term macro
everybody
But some of all individual demands for a particular good or
terrible.
What is the overall demand of Western high school
senior, senior talker Maria?
Pretty new handle.
The heavily.
The handle that her dad works at. I think her family owns me.
Yeah, I'll finish that week. I think her grandpa or not her dad doesn't work that well.
So yeah, I think that I'll, I thought I talked about senior talk about a great
dream then, not one of my classes. So, my family is senior talk to us. I did the head down
account. Are you serious? I spent about $1,000 they last. They said give us. Un-cribe it.
Didn't happen.
Yeah.
Well, you can just say, "There's no fail."
Or, "You go into the person."
And can't even tell me about that, because someone would be like, "There's just voter."
And then, "You're absorbed."
There's no sense of humor.
Don't get jokes. There's no sense of humor.
Don't get jokes.
No, these things.
Comedy is a dead man.
Don't forget the reasons.
There you go.
The graphic ladies and followers.
The individual demand curve are thumbs horizontally to obtain the market demand curve. I'm going to show you two individual demand curves combining each of the market demand curves.
Okay.
One individual second individual final margin one and so far that no rocket science going on.
No rocket. No, right. Thank.
Very slowly. [inaudible] Okay, let's put it two drops.
When we have stock, when we have gems, when the price is $2, we'll demand more hydrogen
cups.
We'll give you a few other four hydrogen cups.
Gems demand.
When the price is $2, we'll demand three hydrogen cups.
So all we're going to do is we're going to take our $2 point,
four and three and put it in a market banker. Very, very simple. We're not doing rocket science had a little math here. $2, market man is seven quantity of ice cream time between the two at $2. For example,
okay, let's move on for you to set maybe a little more
Okay, let's move on to you a second, maybe a little more unzipped. Now, let's talk about a change in quantity.
It changes quantity, man.
It's going to be a movement along the demand curve.
I might ask you to say that I don't think.
Because you will start to get confused.
I am simply talking about a movement along the demand curve.
And that is going from point eight here.
And you want to be there.
That's a movement that is not going to come out
by a change in the price.
A change in the price. Change in the price. Change in the price. Change in the price. Change in the price.
Change in the price.
Change in the price. Walk with the demand is a movement based on price and change. Okay.
Okay.
Okay. Okay, engine quality management.
It's a moving along manager.
We got that?
Okay, there it is.
It's grounded way.
We're gonna change the quality of demand.
At $1, we're gonna require
a $10,000 to the quality of demand.
We're saving the movement this way on this line.
It simply wanna be based on the price change.
Changing the quantity demanded demanded not the demand.
Two different things we're going to talk about.
So a tax, for example, a tax on sellers of ice cream cones
raises the price of ice cream cones
and results in a movement along the demand curve.
So we're going to change the price.
Let's say it goes up from $1 to $2.
And $1 we're going to require eight ice cream cones.
We're going to move it up to $2.
It's going to be four four because we change the price.
And it's going to move to that.
It's simple.
It's.
Emily, are you confused?
You're looking confused.
If you are, now is the time to speak.
Right now is just projects.
It's like a terrible basketball practice.
You're not understanding what play.
It's like a thousand times understanding of traffic questions because any, and you're not understanding what play it's like a thousand times understanding traffic questions because any game you don't understand what play you need.
We both can do that.
You think.
Thanks. based on a change in price. Now we're gonna talk about how do we get that graph to go this way or how do we get that graph
to go up this way to change the overall demand
where price is irrelevant and price is not a factor.
Now, and we're gonna call these ships.
This is where you will have to be able to tell me
our graph that it's a demand graph
goes out that way and same goes in that way.
And some of you already told me a lot of these are going to be exactly
in but we're going to kind of give you what's happened to talk about it.
So change in demand. You notice how I did not pay the payment
stock in payment. I did change in demand. It's a little
language that's going to be very important and it's very
you're going to have to be very important and it's very important.
You're going to have to be very slimy for paying attention to the words that a lot of
tests and the words sound speaking right now.
Change demand, not changing promise.
Now we're not going to talk about price.
Price is irrelevant.
Yeah.
Number one, check the demand curve.
Here's the right or the left.
A shift in the demand curve. You just sort of write it's for the left.
How much we're going to demand a peanut butter, how much we can demand of that law of detail.
How much we can demand of those eggs.
Yes.
But you will always have like a default line to set up.
So this might be, this might be, they would take me one.
Okay.
One.
This might be the man to.
Okay.
Laura. Laura, what is the last one? - No.
- Okay.
- No, it's not.
- All right.
- No, that's not something.
- Okay, the first thing.
- It's not something that you got out of it.
- Not again.
- You know.
- No.
- Excuse me.
- Okay.
- Right, yes.
- Yes.
- Are you?
- Is that all the part of the board?
- No. - Okay. - I have to, for the board, no. Okay, second thing.
It's going to be called by change that voltage,
the quantity demanded at every price.
Any change that comes up on the quantity demanded at every price.
Whatever the price is.
Any change.
Okay.
And post, thanks.
Make sure everybody is understanding.
And.
You know,
movements.
And.
It's.
It's. It's a really interesting.
So, the manual.
Yeah, we follow your own.
Oh, you don't have any grandi.
Yeah.
That's good.
That's good. One of those. [INAUDIBLE] [INAUDIBLE] [INAUDIBLE]
[INAUDIBLE]
[INAUDIBLE] [INAUDIBLE] and how do you say that, keep nice, hard at a time. I like it. You can see it all.
You're hard.
He's a really nice guy.
He didn't really care about the way he choked back his leg.
He didn't come from school and stuff.
His image is unorganized.
OK, we got this.
And if I'm in this.
OK, now let's talk about that.
If Bryce moves it and is determined on once he's made,
let's talk about how long does he get to about that looks like this.
Will we actually move our overall demand,
either increase it or decrease it?
We're going to use an acronym.
And the acronym is going to be POST.
So, ISS.
That is gonna help you memorize it.
And you will be required to remember and define POST.
You're often gonna give the beginning scenarios
in the moment,
but you're gonna have to know what specific
post is out on other circumstances. So the shifters of demand, not the
shifters of quantity demand in me. No demand does not equal quantity
demand in. Know that movement does not equal a shift.
Guys will fall without a trap. Very easily. Number one, take the preference.
That's gonna shift. For example, you think a lot of children like onions.
Dollars, you think dollars like onions? No, generally they know. Add people grow though, do their taste change?
No.
Yes.
Add people grow, do their preference change?
If your taste and preference has changed,
that can move these to man third.
When I was a kid, I hated onions.
Absolutely despised them.
My mom would put onions in spaghetti.
My dad used a pair of books with onions in spaghetti.
Oh, yeah, see, my mom does too.
And I absolutely still hated it, like, moms.
It's that crap out of it.
And you know what mom said when I didn't want to eat it?
Wait, I'll take a guess.
- Do that.
- Yeah, actually, too.
You put it in my mom's room,
you put it on the side.
Tough crap, but she would trust and Spanish.
Tough crap, people.
Peter, 200.
That's good.
That's it.
Okay, take the process number one.
Number two is going to be other,
I mean, later, it's yours.
Now, this one's gonna have two little subtitles. So I would put like
other way to go. So I'm heading and something. Okay, it's other way to do it. So I do think
other way. Last last word, when I asked that interview, a student gave a great answer.
A student said, well, I would expect the demand for peanut butter to change if something happened
to the quantity of bread. Well, what do you mean by that? Well, if there was some type of disease that altered the amount of grain available to make bread as peanut butter and bread or goods
that go together, I would expect people to buy less peanut butter because there's less bread.
Does that make logical sense? Yeah, it makes a complete sense. If there was a bug that wiped out the wheat crop
across the nations and across the world,
making red less available,
people wouldn't buy as much peanut butter
because they're complimentary goods.
People use peanut butter on bread all the time.
If the cattle developed a virus or bacteria that wiped out some of the world's cattle.
Do you think we buy less bread?
Wine, what does cattle produce at weddings? - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. - I'm sorry. What can you substitute? For example, if you're talking about something, you're going to need that.
You're going to need that.
Or change the math.
If there's an Xbox, and then PlayStation comes out
with PlayStation, it's going to affect the demand of Xbox,
because there are substitute goods.
Substitute goods.
And substitute goods are usually going to decrease the demand because if I have an Xbox and then PlayStation comes out of the main PlayStation.
So when it comes out, hey, we're beginning to do the PlayStation.
Maybe I might go by the PlayStation instead of the Xbox and my demand for Xbox is going to decrease.
Not because the price changes at the Xbox
because there's a substitute good.
The Xbox could raise the price by $100
and if somebody comes out and makes a PlayStation
and I buy the PlayStation,
has nothing to do with the price of the Xbox.
As soon as there's a substitute good out there, okay?
And pencils substitute goods.
Another one under other good age goods
can be very important for us to understand.
It's going to be compliments.
Compliments.
You have to think of compliment each other.
For example, bread and butter.
Peanut butter and bread.
Lamb and tuna fish.
- Mm, mm-hmm.
- All of you are more than familiar with that for comedy? - Yes. and tuna fish. [inaudible] [inaudible] [inaudible]
[inaudible]
[inaudible] [inaudible] - I'm gonna jell in. Next one, the E, it's expectations.
Expectations.
The example I gave last class period
dealt with avocados.
What did we get?
You guys know where the United States gets
more avocados?
- Spectrales.
- You know who, at this time,
for ranses, Mexican avocados, apartments? - America. - America. You know who often times Horaces Mexican avocado parmes
I'm here
You guys know who often times are asses Mexican avocado
They're a lot of the cartels do and oftentimes what cartels do in order to have an income source is they will kidnap
Mexican avocado farmers white or daughter or son or themselves and they'll say if you want to your daughter back mother back white back you're gonna have to pay us $10,000 or give us 10 acres of your avocado.
That's what the cartels do. Okay, so let's say. It kind of is happening. You guys don't kind of know that growth and power
of the Mexican cartels.
It's it's really gross.
So it's.
It's dangerous.
OK, so let's say the cartels were to say, hey, whole world,
hey, United States, you know what we're going to do?
In January 1, 2025, the Mexican cartels,
we're going gonna take over the or buy more, buy less of. Buy more, buy more. Because they're not expensive right now.
Or if it's apples, and they're going to take over
the couple orders, and they can go buy a bunch of apples
right now.
And I'm going to do something like that.
Because you would expect the future, the price of it
is to increase the transfer.
But the expectation of a future event
is going to then have a direct correlation to the end.
In case of the case of the working
with the bigger end goal.
- Well, I was like, yeah, but now that one's different.
(mumbles)
- How many people have you got wiped over red?
- There was just kind of a, you know,
nobody said like,
(indistinct)
In regards to the first thing.
But if COVID happened,
it's setting people over.
What's a better example?
'Cause it's not like people get their shoes.
It's not better.
It's just, whatever nature decides besides and somebody's used it.
But in COVID, it was more like, people have a toilet set.
They didn't want to be left after it.
It was a people have a choice of how my alcohol
can fit in the toilet.
Because when I went outside to watch my dog,
every last recycle bin was just full of things.
That's a choice you get to me just to leave.
Where I'd like to look for something
and before you get it let me talk to you okay you don't get to be like hey I need Okay, that's a good thing.
All right.
Yeah, let's love you.
I am going to begin.
Here's an example of interrupt.
No one, do you think that when I was younger, I was growing up?
One of the items that my family ate a lot, especially as a child, was free volities and photos.
- Invis, - Invis and rice.
Why, I ate a lot of Invis and rice, kid?
Other than the fact that like,
you know, the bong dong thing and my mom is
spanning two sheets of tea, it's very cheap and expensive.
A good that we were to consider an inferior good.
Not that feeds the brand's mark, but it's just considered a cheapest barrier good.
It's like Tom Rama.
I had a lot of Tom Rama when I was a kid too, and many of you will too when you're in color
because of me.
However, when my mom's income increased and she got a little bit more education, a few
more degrees, a little bit more experience, a better job.
Do you think you made as much beans and rice?
No.
So he should tell me that it is a pump.
He's going to affect the demand.
He comes with me to affect the demand.
Do you think I ate lobster tails when I was growing up?
No.
I was close.
Do you think now, at a point in my life,
do you think I buy as much beans and rice? It's nice. No, unless I want cultural, kind of, meal.
Okay.
And I'll make this on my grandkids.
Not when I make it.
It's just when I make it, it's like pigeon-free.
So I'm not going to eat it.
But if my income increases, I'm going to be more likely to buy goods considered new
programs.
So a normal good.
We're going to call that any good that you buy when your income goes
up.
Because if I'm rich, why would I continue buying a couple noodles?
I will.
Again, you can easily say, well, Mr. Sputter, what if somebody is very frugal?
What if somebody wants to just, "What if somebody really likes kapanoodles?"
Of course, that happens.
That's the what-it game.
But economics isn't playing the what-it games, playing the Sedera's Paribus game.
What is the most likely to happen when someone's income increases?
And when someone's income increases, their purchase and consumption of normal goods increases.
But beans and rice,
top ramen, cup of noodles, hot dog, those are going to be considered inferior goods.
So the opposite exists as well. As income goes down,
or excuse me, as income goes up, you buy less of inferior goods.
But as your income decreases,
you will buy more inferior goods.
Make sense?
If you are poor, you're gonna buy cheap goods.
If you make more money,
you're gonna buy more expensive goods.
Sederos Parovas.
Assuming nobody's a cheapskate,
assuming nobody's saving for some big purchase,
assuming nobody's frugal,
assuming that's not somebody's favorite food,
because we could simply sit here all day long
and say, well, let's just vote up.
What if beans and rice is somebody's favorite food?
And what if somebody just loves top ramen?
Okay, yes, I understand it.
That's the exception.
That's could happen.
But that's not what we're talking about when
we talk about economics.
OK, yes, it's going to be size of market.
Size of market.
Meaning there's a lot of people who
will invite a particular product.
The demand for hotel rooms will skyrocket
in Portland building, I mean baseball stadium.
Because all of those workers are gonna have to be shipped
in from somewhere, purely not Portland.
And they're gonna have to build a baseball stadium.
They will have to stay somewhere
for an extended credit time.
Those buyers are going to be buyers of home hotel rooms.
Because if that happens, there will be a thousand workers in downtown Portland, on south waterfront, trying to build a baseball stadium, and a lot of that needs a place to
live. That's a size of market increase. And the last one is going to be special circumstances.
For example, if there's a Winter Olympics, you demand for getting services going skyrocket. Yes. Yes. Special certain thing.
Oh, yeah, can you pass it on? I can pay a billion can't help this. Thank you. What you got today,
the title. Well, and it's a new bottle. Something you can stop that that I thought it didn't have my name. The team is a good place.
Thank you.
My turn to understand.
You think it's curious.
I don't know why this is not safe.
I don't know.
Yeah, all this. Now, that's probably why I'm too asked to sometimes confusing questions because people Thank you. Let me answer your your country.
Or the language. Please.
Let's do it.
We need to do it.
You need to do it.
This is the biggest.
Yeah, this is what I was playing.
Usually. Once we look at this picture, then what we're
going to do in the packet earlier is passing out. Instead, demand curve. If the demand
curve is going to be characterized by a default line, we will have D1. After you have D1, you
can have a line that's going to move, that's going to shift the graph. I'm not talking
about root in the graph, I'm talking to shift the graph. I'm not talking about looping the graph.
I'm talking about shifting your graph.
The switch needs to pay careful intention between quantity demanded and demand and movements versus shifts, because they both mean two different things.
This is talking about the shift.
A shift is post. A movement is price.
The interval attention.
If we have a line here,
we're going to follow the demand curve D1.
If it moves out, there's an increase in demand.
Not an increase in fonts and you may have it,
but an increase in demand,
it's going to move it out.
It's going to be a new demand curve.
If it moves in and demand decreases because of
expectations, face and preferences change,
expectations change, income bill, up or income goes down,
it's going to move this way.
Okay. It's going to be a decrease in demand,
we're going to call that degree.
That is why it's fundamentalist the United States government.
We always look at what is
the income of the average income of
the United States citizens per capita per person.
If the average income of
the United States citizens increases,
our government knows,
okay, economically, if the income of individuals in the United States citizens increases, our government knows, okay, economically,
if the income of individuals in the United States per capita increases, the demand for
normal goods is going to increase as well. And then how do we increase our production
possibilities for demand of a normal goods or income decreases? How do we shift that?
And then if the demand for our income decreases in the United States, quick happen, that tells the United States government, you know, the, the
equivalent of American citizens, this decreased by $10,000, meaning that Americans
are going to buy more in periods. So how do we even get there or enough in period
that someone buy all of it's connected? Okay. And that's what we're gonna do today, okay?
So, next class period, all right?